{"sid": "MY2WUIH1TGEX_main", "calc_equals_delay": 3, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 369339, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 369341, "question": "7+3+7+68", "correct_answer": 85, "events": [["submit", 380738]], "time_left_end": "289", "answered_time": 380738, "user_answer": "85", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "289", "question_time_start": 380738, "question": "16+786", "correct_answer": 802, "events": [["submit", 391736]], "time_left_end": "278", "answered_time": 391736, "user_answer": "802", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "278", "question_time_start": 391736, "question": "9+3+13", "correct_answer": 25, "events": [["submit", 397641]], "time_left_end": "272", "answered_time": 397640, "user_answer": "25", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "272", "question_time_start": 397641, "question": "3+79+88", "correct_answer": 170, "events": [["submit", 407819]], "time_left_end": "262", "answered_time": 407819, "user_answer": "170", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "262", "question_time_start": 407819, "question": "4+3+8+98", "correct_answer": 113, "events": [["submit", 420384]], "time_left_end": "249", "answered_time": 420384, "user_answer": "113", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "249", "question_time_start": 420384, "question": "3+7+4+24", "correct_answer": 38, "events": [["submit", 428611]], "time_left_end": "241", "answered_time": 428611, "user_answer": "38", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "241", "question_time_start": 428611, "question": "23+37", "correct_answer": 60, "events": [["submit", 434535]], "time_left_end": "235", "answered_time": 434535, "user_answer": "60", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "235", "question_time_start": 434535, "question": "76+47", "correct_answer": 123, "events": [["submit", 441178]], "time_left_end": "229", "answered_time": 441178, "user_answer": "123", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "229", "question_time_start": 441178, "question": "3+44+28", "correct_answer": 75, "events": [["submit", 457257]], "time_left_end": "213", "answered_time": 457257, "user_answer": "75", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "213", "question_time_start": 457257, "question": "4+7+77", "correct_answer": 88, "events": [["submit", 464681]], "time_left_end": "205", "answered_time": 464681, "user_answer": "88", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 464681, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "205", "question_time_start": 464681, "question": "4+3+3+47", "correct_answer": 57, "events": [["submit", 472741]], "time_left_end": "197", "answered_time": 472741, "user_answer": "57", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "197", "question_time_start": 472741, "question": "3+58+29", "correct_answer": 90, "events": [["submit", 485571]], "time_left_end": "184", "answered_time": 485571, "user_answer": "90", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "184", "question_time_start": 485571, "question": "7+9+53", "correct_answer": 69, "events": [["submit", 496149]], "time_left_end": "174", "answered_time": 496149, "user_answer": "69", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "174", "question_time_start": 496149, "question": "6+4+6+93", "correct_answer": 109, "events": [["submit", 502857]], "time_left_end": "167", "answered_time": 502857, "user_answer": "109", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "167", "question_time_start": 502857, "question": "37+916", "correct_answer": 953, "events": [["submit", 519875]], "time_left_end": "150", "answered_time": 519875, "user_answer": "953", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "150", "question_time_start": 519876, "question": "87+88", "correct_answer": 175, "events": [["submit", 527903]], "time_left_end": "142", "answered_time": 527903, "user_answer": "175", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "142", "question_time_start": 527904, "question": "9+96+39", "correct_answer": 144, "events": [["submit", 538196]], "time_left_end": "132", "answered_time": 538196, "user_answer": "144", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "132", "question_time_start": 538196, "question": "93+79", "correct_answer": 172, "events": [["submit", 551877]], "time_left_end": "118", "answered_time": 551877, "user_answer": "172", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "118", "question_time_start": 551878, "question": "9+8+8+24", "correct_answer": 49, "events": [["submit", 560207]], "time_left_end": "110", "answered_time": 560207, "user_answer": "49", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "110", "question_time_start": 560208, "question": "7+9+86", "correct_answer": 102, "events": [["submit", 576493]], "time_left_end": "93", "answered_time": 576493, "user_answer": "102", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 576493, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "93", "question_time_start": 576493, "question": "97+373", "correct_answer": 470, "events": [["submit", 583465]], "time_left_end": "86", "answered_time": 583465, "user_answer": "470", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "86", "question_time_start": 583465, "question": "9+4+6+37", "correct_answer": 56, "events": [["submit", 593506]], "time_left_end": "76", "answered_time": 593506, "user_answer": "56", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "76", "question_time_start": 593506, "question": "73+53", "correct_answer": 126, "events": [["submit", 600450]], "time_left_end": "69", "answered_time": 600450, "user_answer": "126", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "69", "question_time_start": 600450, "question": "6+39+36", "correct_answer": 81, "events": [["submit", 607094]], "time_left_end": "63", "answered_time": 607094, "user_answer": "81", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "63", "question_time_start": 607094, "question": "9+4+47", "correct_answer": 60, "events": [["submit", 612181]], "time_left_end": "58", "answered_time": 612181, "user_answer": "60", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "58", "question_time_start": 612182, "question": "4+3+9+19", "correct_answer": 35, "events": [["submit", 619368]], "time_left_end": "50", "answered_time": 619368, "user_answer": "35", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "50", "question_time_start": 619368, "question": "7+3+7+77", "correct_answer": 94, "events": [["submit", 627000]], "time_left_end": "43", "answered_time": 627000, "user_answer": "94", "user_correct": "True", "score": "27"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "43", "question_time_start": 627002, "question": "56+29", "correct_answer": 85, "events": [["submit", 633884]], "time_left_end": "36", "answered_time": 633884, "user_answer": "85", "user_correct": "True", "score": "28"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "36", "question_time_start": 633884, "question": "4+24+16", "correct_answer": 44, "events": [["submit", 642276]], "time_left_end": "28", "answered_time": 642276, "user_answer": "44", "user_correct": "True", "score": "29"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "28", "question_time_start": 642277, "question": "9+9+26", "correct_answer": 44, "events": [["submit", 648467]], "time_left_end": "21", "answered_time": 648467, "user_answer": "44", "user_correct": "True", "score": "30"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 648468, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "21", "question_time_start": 648468, "question": "3+6+18", "correct_answer": 27, "events": [["submit", 652988]], "time_left_end": "17", "answered_time": 652988, "user_answer": "27", "user_correct": "True", "score": "31"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "17", "question_time_start": 652988, "question": "4+47+53", "correct_answer": 104, "events": [["submit", 658695]], "time_left_end": "11", "answered_time": 658695, "user_answer": "104", "user_correct": "True", "score": "32"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "11", "question_time_start": 658695, "question": "8+7+8+83", "correct_answer": 106, "events": []}}}}}